especiallyyours.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Especially Yours

**ESPECIALLY YOURS PRIVACY POLICY**

_Last Updated May 2018_

At Especially Yours your privacy is as important to us as it is to you. Our Privacy Policy defines how Especially Yours protects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes:

  * What personal information we collect and when it is collected
  * How your information is used and protected
  * When and with whom your information is shared
  * What to do if you feel your personal information has been compromised

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by Specialty Commerce Corp., which offers many different websites for many different business purposes. As this Privacy Policy applies to all of our websites, they are collectively referred to as Website throughout this policy. The Website is also governed by its Terms of Use. If any of the terms of this Privacy Policy directly conflict with the Terms of Use, the terms of this Privacy Policy will apply.   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our Website or write to us at:  
OR  
_Privacy and Compliance_  
__Especially Yours_  
_P.O. Box 105__  
_South Easton, MA 02375_  
_1-800-748-6910_

**Information We Collect**    
This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information, which is information that Especially Yours collects from you as a customer that specifically identifies you as an individual. This information is collected to provide you with the products and services you have requested as well as to provide a pleasant shopping experience now and to improve the shopping experience in the future.

While we limit the information we collect, we do collect Personal Information when you:

  * Place an order from our catalogs or on our Website
  * Create an account on our Website
  * Make a purchase via phone, online or through our factory store
  * Return an item or make an exchange
  * Inquire about our products or services or contact customer service
  * Request a catalog
  * Sign up for Especially Yours email updates or other promotional materials
  * Enter a contest or sweepstakes
  * Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
  * Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect Personal Information including:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Telephone number
  * Fax number
  * Email address
  * Transaction information
  * Credit card, debit card, or checking account information
  * Age/Date of Birth (in conjunction with promotions, for credit card applications and credit checks)  

In order to provide you with a better shopping experience and to improve the quality of our services, we may combine the information you submit under your account with other information that we may receive from you, from third parties, or with other public demographic information. We maintain this information, along with a record of your purchases, in a restricted database.

Also, our Website is not directed at collecting Personal Information from children and we do not actively collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**    
At Especially Yours, we always want to provide you with the easiest and best possible shopping experience from the time you begin looking for products and services through the delivery of your requested items. The information that we collect lets us meet this goal by allowing us to:

  * Customize your shopping experience
  * Confirm, process and track your orders
  * Provide the products and services you request
  * Contact you with questions or status updates regarding an order
  * Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online
  * Respond to your customer service inquiries or requests
  * Identify your product and service preferences
  * Communicate great values and featured items to you
  * Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
  * Send you Especially Yours email updates
  * Improve our merchandise selection, Website, retail experience and customer service
  * Provide information concerning products you have purchased
  * Prevent or mitigate fraud and credit risk
  * Administer billing and payment for your purchases
  * Administer promotions, contests and sweepstakes
  * Comply with applicable law, legal procedures, requirements, regulations and statutes
  * Especially Yours does offer some of our services in connection with affiliated companies as well as other third parties. Third party websites may have different privacy practices than described in this Privacy Policy. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policies associated with third party websites as this Privacy Policy applies only to the Especially Yours Website, Especially Yours' services, and Especially Yours' handling of Personal Information. 
  * When you provide personal information to one of our Specialty Commerce Corp. brands we may share that information with our other sister brands (see <http://www.scdirect.com/>) for marketing purposes.

**Information Sharing Practices**  
We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.  
Personal information. We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with: 

  * Authorized service providers: We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * Business partners: When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our websites, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that business partner.
  * Other affiliated businesses: We are part of a family of businesses for cooperative marketing purposes ("Affiliates"). We may share information we collect, including personal information, with the Affiliates. Sharing information with our Affiliates enables us to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you. Our Affiliates also will comply with applicable privacy and security laws and, at a minimum, in any commercial e-mail they send to you, will give you the opportunity to choose not to receive such e-mail messages in the future.

Personal Information that you provide to third party websites may be sent to Especially Yours in order to deliver the services you have requested. You can be assured that we will process Personal Information that we receive from these websites in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.

**Personal information**  
We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with: 

  * **Authorized service providers:** We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * **Business partners:** When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our websites, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that business partner. 
  * **Other affiliated businesses:** We are part of a family of businesses for cooperative marketing purposes ("Affiliates"). We may share information we collect, including personal information, with the Affiliates. Sharing information with our Affiliates enables us to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you. Our Affiliates also will comply with applicable privacy and security laws and, at a minimum, in any commercial e-mail they send to you, will give you the opportunity to choose not to receive such e-mail messages in the future.

**ATTENTION CANADIAN CUSTOMERS**  
Effective July 1, 2014, Canada’s new anti-spam legislation goes into effect. To abide by this law, we will only send emails to Canadian customers with whom we have a business relationship. When you subscribed to our email distribution list or purchased from us prior to 07/01/14, we assumed a business relationship with you.

If you no longer wish to continue this relationship, please unsubscribe using the link we provide at the bottom of our promotional emails.

If you have not consented to be on our email distribution list, but wish to do so now, please click [here](http://www.especiallyyours.com/ancillary/emailsignup.do).

**ATTENTION CALIFORNIA CUSTOMERS**  
Pursuant to California law, you have the right to obtain a list of organizations to which we rent or disclose information for direct marketing purposes. To request this list, fax your name, mailing address, and email address to us at 1-508-238-1965.

If you no longer wish to receive promotional emails from Especially Yours, please unsubscribe using the link we provide at the bottom of our messages. 

If you have not consented to be on our email distribution list, but wish to do so now, please click [here](http://www.especiallyyours.com/ancillary/emailsignup.do).

**ATTENTION EUROPEAN UNION (EU) CUSTOMERS**  
Especially Yours complies with the EU's May 25, 2018, General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) regarding the collection, use, retention, and transfer of personal Information from citizens of EU member countries.

If you are an EU citizen and wish to review the personal information you have shared with Especially Yours, or wish for us to delete that information, please email us at [customerservice@especiallyyours.com](mailto:CustomerService@EspeciallyYours.com). As per GDPR guidelines, we will complete your request within 30 days of submission. 

**Safe, Secure Ordering**    
We respect your right to privacy, and ensure that your personal information is kept completely safe and secure at all times, whether ordering by phone or online. We occasionally share our customer list with reputable, carefully screened companies whose products we feel may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your name, please let us know at 1-800-748-6910 

**Choices for Personal Information**    
To further improve your shopping experience, Especially Yours partners with third party vendors such as Google Analytics to evaluate how the Website is used and to provide continuous improvement for our services. Like most websites, we use "cookies" for a variety of purposes to improve your visits to the Website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to the hard drive on your computer for record keeping purposes. For example, we use cookies to understand which web pages are visited, how often they are visited, to remember you when you return to the Website, and to generally make the Website more user friendly.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You may decide to reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do decide to refuse all cookies please be aware that some Website features and Especially Yours services may be unavailable or may not function properly.

**Choices for Receiving Promotional Material**    
You may also decide to opt out of receiving promotional mail and/or email from Especially Yours. Simply notify us of this decision by one of these methods:

  * Follow the unsubscribe link on any promotional email received from Especially Yours. 
  * Send an email to us at [CustomerService@EspeciallyYours.com](mailto:CustomerService@EspeciallyYours.com)
  * Call us toll free at 1-800-952-5926
  * Fax us at 1-508-238-1965
  * Write to us at:  

_Especially Yours_  
__P.O. Box 105__  
_South Easton, MA 02375_

Please note that any opt-out request sent via postal mail may take at least sixty (60) days to become effective. You may still receive email or postal mail from other affiliated companies and third parties if they have received your email or postal address from sources other than Especially Yours or as a result of their own transactions or experiences with you. You will also continue to receive email or postal mail if you request to hear from us again at a later date.

**Ownership of Customer Information  **  
As a direct marketing company, Especially Yours places a significant value on the information compiled about our registered visitors, catalog requesters and customers. This information is essential to the operation of our company and constitutes a corporate asset of substantial value.

  * In any business transaction involving the purchase or sale of assets by Especially Yours or its affiliated business entities, this customer information may be purchased or sold just as any other piece of company-owned property. By registering, requesting a catalog or making a purchase on our web site, you give us your consent to the purchase or sale of this information should such a business transaction take place
  * We may provide you with links to other companies or organizations which we feel provide useful information, services or products related to the Especially Yours web site. While we believe these organizations to be reputable and committed to consumer privacy, we cannot be responsible for the policies or practices of those who have sites linked to ours.
  * We may disclose and/or transfer Personal Information to a third party in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale (including any transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving Especially Yours or its affiliated companies or as part of a corporate reorganization, asset sale, or other change in corporate control.

**Analytics Tracking and Third Party Advertising**  
The analytics and third-party advertising applications we employ use cookies to collect web-viewing data about your shopping experience. These cookies (which do not include personally identifying information) allow us to personalize your experience on our site and serve customized advertising on other web sites. For more information about the non-personally identifiable information Google and other third-party advertising companies collect, and about the opportunity to opt out of such data collection, please visit [ http://google.com/doubleclick](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/#). Google has additional information available about their [ Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/143465?hl=en&rd=2).

We use web metric vendors to gather information that helps us understand how you use our website. You may opt out of the Google advertising cookie by visiting the [ Google advertising opt-out page](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en) or [ Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

**Information Security**    
Especially Yours processes Personal Information for the purposes for which it was collected. The information is processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy, any additional privacy notices that may be associated with the service we are supplying, applicable law, or your authorization or consent.

We maintain reasonable and appropriate standards to safeguard your Personal Information. All on-line transactions which require the exchange of credit card information are initiated and completed in a secure environment for the protection of our customers. 

**Data Integrity**    
Especially Yours takes reasonable steps to verify that the Personal Information we store and process is accurate, complete and current. We also depend on our customers to update or correct their online profiles and to contact us with changes in Personal Information whenever necessary by one of the following means:

  * Follow the unsubscribe link on any promotional email received from Especially Yours
  * Send an email to us at [CustomerService@EspeciallyYours.com](mailto:CustomerService@EspeciallyYours.com)
  * Call us toll free at 1-800-952-5926
  * Fax us at 1-508-238-1965
  * Write to us at:  

_Especially Yours_  
__P.O. Box 105__  
_South Easton, MA 02375_

Unless otherwise required by law or for legitimate business purposes, we will make good faith efforts to correct or delete such data at your request when you notify us of an error or change in your Personal Information. To prevent unauthorized changes to someone's Personal Information, we ask individual customers to positively identify themselves before processing such requests.

**Policy Enforcement**    
Especially Yours regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Especially Yours' treatment of Personal Information to us through the Website or by writing to us at the email or postal mail address contained at the beginning of this document.

If we receive a written complaint, it is Especially Yours' policy to contact the complaining customer regarding his or her concerns. We will investigate complaints promptly and diligently to address your concerns and resolve any dispute quickly.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**    
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified by its effective date found at the top of this document.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at the email or postal mail address contained at the beginning of this document.
